YEKINI SAHEED AKANFE

Address: Line 1, zone 1, Balogun Street Off Alakia Isebo Ibadan Oyo State.

Email: Saheed12020@gmail.com

Phone: 08130967990, 08081680725.

PERSONAL DATA:

Sex: - Male

Marital Status: - Married

Age: - 05-01-1992

State of Origin: - Oyo State

OBJECTIVE:

To obtain an entry-level management position within an organization that would give chance for the display of my skills and knowledge.

PROFILE:

A graduate of Business Administration and Management, Adept and experienced at driving organizational growth, customer service and problem solving through the application of my communication skills, and experience. Intuitive, sociable and receptive to all and diverse culture.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

> 2008-2012

Front Office Supervisor at M&K Hotel and suite Alakia Ibadan, Oyo State.

Responsibility:

Keep clear and comprehensive records of guest room and booking and all billing for accountability and future reference.

Report issues of maintenance and malfunction appliance to the manager for quick repair in order to ensure guests comfort and satisfaction.

Receiving of guests to the hotel and attending to their enquires.

> 2014-2015

Marketer at Polaris Bank Ondo Branch, Ondo State.

Responsibility:

- ★ Responsible for coordinating and implementing the marketing & promotion campaigns for the bank.
- ★ Develops all forms of marketing materials including branch digital and other promotional material and marketing budget management.

≥ 2017

Industry, Jigawa State.

Responsibility:

- ★ Training individuals with domestic skills.
- ★ Designing curriculum for skills acquisition.

> 2017—2020

Procurement & Logistics Assistant Manager @ Partnet Metropolitan Company Ibadan, Oyo state.

Responsibility:

- ★ Ensure that the Company makes wise purchase of goods and services to resell or used.
- ★ Monitor use of materials and resources and ensure quality record keeping also ensure that organization works with competent and reliable suppliers.
- ★ Helps to protect the organization from incurring losses by minimizing fraud and waste.
- ★ Ensure that purchase reports of stakeholders for decision making and maintain database for suppliers for Organisation.
- ★ Develop logistics along with support plans, budget requirements and deployment timelines for new operations.
- ★ Develop logistical plans for current operations and logistics contingency plans.
- ★ Develop and execute tools and methodologies to enable effective implementation of logistic plans.
- ★ Ensure accountable, timely and cost-effective release of peacekeeping cargos along with personnel.

EDUCATION:

Interlink Polytechnic ijebu-jesa, Osun State

2015-2017

Higher National Diploma in Business Administration and Mgt.

Interlink Polytechnic Ijebu-Ijesa, Osun State.

2012-2014

National Diploma in Business Administration. and Mgt

Monatan High School, Iyalode Ibadan, Oyo Stat

2002-2008

National Examination Council (NECO)

West African Examination Council (WAEC)

East Gate Primary School, Gbagi Ibadan, Oyo State

1995-2002

Primary School Leaving Certificate

PROFESSIONAL COURSE ATTENDED:

iReign Class of Professional Excellence, (iRCPE) UK.

2018

through iReign Classique Consult Nigeria, (iRCCN), Kaduna.

Competence Certificate in Human Resource Management (HRM).

ADDITIONAL SKILLS AND INTERESTS:

Computer Skills: Working proficiency in Microsoft Suite, Excel, Data Analysis.

Language Skills: Yoruba and English

Driven Skills: Car, Bus and any others Vehicle, with Valid Driver's license.

LEADERSHIP:

Faculty president Interlink Polytechnic, ijebu-jesa, Osun State. 2017

NYSC Social director Fanisau Orientation Camp, Jigawa State. 2018

Transport Secretary at The Redeemed Christian Corps Fellowship 2018

(R.C.C.F) Jigawa state.

HOBBIES:

Reading, Meeting new people, Travelling, Driven Vehicle, Research development and Data Analysis.

REFEREES:

MR. AJIBADE ADEOLU

Head of Marketing

Ibadan Electricity Distribution Company, (IBEDC) Ilesha Business unit

Osun State.

08033769861

MR. TOSIN OMOLE

Managing Director

Ere-City Microfinance Bank Ere-Ijesha, Osun State

08037174030